HA JUNG-WOO
IM SOO-JUNG
KIM JUN-HAN
KRYSTAL JUNG
SHIM EUN-KYUNG
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
NINE YEARS AGO
Crazy.
Hwal-sung.
Huh?
Oh?
What is it?
Really?
- Wow!
- Wait a minute, Hwal-sung!
- Be careful.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
What should we do?
Seriously?
You worked hard, Yi-gyeong.
So did you, Hwal-sung.
What should we do?
Is this real?
Two lines.
Wow.
Hey.
Hey, but can you walk around like this
while leaving behind Yi-gyeong?
How many weeks has it been?
It's been 16 weeks.
Wow, it's just starting.
I can't believe you're going to be a dad.
I'm really worried.
Want a drink first?
I'll just accept it.
I have to leave early tomorrow.
Yi-gyeong is telling me
to prepare becoming a civil servant.
I mean, I've never even tried.
How can I suddenly become one?
Don't do that. Not doing it
is your way of being patriotic.
Right?
For my country,
I'm not becoming a civil servant.
But why did you suddenly want to meet up?
My friend,
do you want to be a building owner?
What?
Let's stretch out.
Mother, I'm here.
One, two, three, four.
Breathe comfortably.
- Seven, eight, nine, ten.
- Oh.
Two, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight, nine.
Raise them up.
- One, two, three...
- The child,
whether daughter or son,
is part of the Jeon family. Remember that.
Yes, Mother. Of course.
Behave properly.
Yes.
Mother, by the way...
Actually, I'm preparing something.
For Yi-gyeong and the baby.
So I was wondering
if you could help me a little bit.
Let's talk after the baby is born.
Oh, sure.
I think it's done.
- Yes, it went through.
- Okay.
- Wait right here.
- Sure.
I'll get the receipt.
Hello, landlord.
Crazy bastard.
Well, if you were paying,
I would have gone
somewhere expensive.
You're really drunk, aren't you?
Anyway, let's plan to
have a meal together soon
with Seon and Yi-gyeong.
Yes, sounds good.
Anyway, thank you for
the meal today, landlord.
Get home safe, landlord.
- Oh, thank you.
- Yes, you're the best.
Thank you.
- Here.
- Have a good night.
- Let's go.
- Yes, have a good night.
Yes, Mother?
What?
Yi-gyeong!
The mother was able
to overcome the critical point.
What about the baby?
INCORRECT PASSWORD / PLEASE RE-ENTER
What are you doing,
sneaking in here?
Mother, but did you
change the password or something?
Don't even think about coming home
until Yi-gyeong gets better.
W-What do you mean?
I need to take care of Yi-gyeong.
This is already
the second miscarriage, right?
Listen to me carefully.
I don't know about other things,
but a couple that loses a child
can't recover.
Get ready to sort it out.
Mother!
Yi-gyeong!
Yi-gyeong.
SU-JONG
What is it?
What's with you?
What?
The final payment. What happened?
I'm sorry, buddy.
I think it's going to be tough.
Seriously, this bastard!
How can you be saying that?
Mom went a bit overboard this time, right?
You didn't do anything wrong.
I handled it well.
Let's just keep a low profile for now.
Mom's really heartbroken.
Okay.
- No.
- Huh?
I'm still not fully recovered.
Also, can you clean that up?
It's really painful to see.
So why did you take the urn?
Don't you know how hard
it has been for Yi-gyeong?
I just thought Yi-gyeong
would want to see it one last time.
You really don't understand anything.
Let's go in. We're here.
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
Hold on, who is this?
- Huh?
- Hwal-sung,
you're going to die today.
What?
See you in hell, my friend.
Listen.
We planned on
making it seem like
he came to check out an auction item
and ended up falling.
Just help us carry him to that spot.
Jeez, making me do everything.
What is this?
What are you guys doing?
Don't come near!
What?
Don't come any closer!
What are you doing?
How cute.
Are you going to hit me?
Hit me.
Let's have some more
friendly deaths today.
I followed because I was anxious.
Damn it...
Get some rest.
Ae-su, let's start with that.
How many minutes has it been?
- It's been about five minutes.
- Damn it.
- Stay away.
- Do not touch the patient.
- Step away from the patient.
- Back off.
Please press
the flashing orange button.
Electric shock will be administered.
Performing CPR.
Ae-su.
Min Hwal-sung, wake up!
It worked.
It worked. Min Hwal-sung is back.
Hwal-sung, are you okay?
We did it.
It's done.
Yes.
Honey?
Honey.
Honey!
- Huh?
- Are you okay?
Yes.
Are you okay, honey?
- Yes. Honey, you okay?
- Yes.
What about Hwal-sung?
Min Hwal-sung is awake.
Okay.
NO ENTRY EXCEPT FOR AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL
- Is it done?
- Yes, it's done. Let's go.
You handle the rest.
Right.
What about him?
We can make it out safely, right?
Of course.
REAL CAPITAL JONAH
Contact me anytime
if you need help.
Auntie,
are you okay?
How about you?
To have parents who are murderers.
That's not something
you should say.
Are you saying I did something wrong?
I think there are lines
that shouldn't be crossed.
Your parents are the ones
who crossed the line first.
Just because
someone else did wrong
doesn't mean I can too.
I disguised it as a falling accident
and took care of it.
Since it's done,
can we take Da-rae now?
What about your confession?
If they find the body, I'll do it then.
Da-rae.
Is Uncle Hwal-sung
really dead?
I'll explain
everything later.
Let's go.
- Okay, let's go.
- Let's go.
Wait a minute.
- Hey, slow down.
- Okay.
JEON YI-GYEONG
Yes, Ms. Jeon?
What brings you here at this hour?
Detective Koh,
please come to Seyoon Building
right now.
Is something wrong, Ms. Jeon?
Your voice doesn't sound good.
The suspect that
you want to catch is right here.
You'll know who it is once you see.
What is it?
Let's go.
W-Where to?
Sit still.
If you keep this up, I'll zap you again.
I'm not some electric eel.
Why keep zapping?
Here are the keys.
People will come to see the building
in the morning.
Okay, okay!
But,
could you do me a favor?
What is it?
I really need to pee.
What do you want me to do about it?
Could you just pull down my pants a bit?
You must be crazy.
Hey, you won't even
let me go to the bathroom
anyway.
Come on.
Don't be like this.
Just pull it from behind!
Gosh.
Please respect my rights.
Come on,
I feel like I'm going to burst.
Ugh.
Ah!
Hey!
Get off!
Ah!
Damn it!
Jeez!
Damn.
What is that? An IV?
Damn it.
Jeez.
Seon, you take Da-rae
and leave.
Get going first.
It's okay. Just go.
I'll talk it out first.
Didn't he have
any last words before dying?
I don't know.
When Hwal-sung was dying,
did he leave any last words?
That he was sorry
and that when the kid is born,
to say only nice things.
Did Hwal-sung know
that I was pregnant?
Yes.
LOAN HEAVEN
Keep those bastards
locked up.
They pulled a stunt.
You got tricked!
Right until the end...
Gi Su-jong!
Damn!
Hurry and catch him!
Get him!
Get in!
Grab him!
What is this?
Huh?
- Hey.
- Huh?
Huh?
- Is this heaven?
- Huh?
- This is Korea.
What are you doing here?
Huh?
Where's Su-jong?
Oh, Seyoon Building.
To save Da-rae.
Da-rae?
Gosh, you don't know?
Your wife kidnapped Da-rae.
Wait a minute.
By the way,
thanks for saving me.
You're welcome.
They cleaned up well.
Clean what?
Give it.
- Open up!
- You bastard!
You bastard!
Damn it!
REAL CAPITAL JONAH
Come out!
Open up!
REAL CAPITAL JONAH
Answer the phone!
We're on the 3rd floor. Help us.
REAL CAPITAL JONAH
HELP US, SEYOON BUILDING
Help us, Seyoon Building.
Shall we go?
Yes, let's go.
NO ENTRY
Hey, go up
and find the girl.
Got it.
Damn it!
Hurry and open it!
Damn!
Sir.
Damn it!
Move aside.
How are you
going to get out this time?
Try that again, you bastard.
Huh?
Hey, who are you guys?
Hello.
Who the hell?
Ugh!
Damn it.
What's this?
Why is there a fire?
Damn it!
Ugh!
Damn!
Ah!
Hey!
Whoa!
What's this? What's going on?
Min Hwal-sung?
Don't come!
We are in front of
Seyoon Building at 52 Sejeong-ro.
Min Hwal-sung!
There's a fire.
The building is on fire.
Min Hwal-sung!
LOAN HEAVEN
Huh?
Yi-gyeong!
Seon.
Seon, Da-rae.
Please stop this.
Calm down, Yi-gyeong.
Don't do it.
Yi-gyeong, please stop.
D-Don't come closer.
Don't come closer!
Yi-gyeong, please calm down.
We can
go back to the way things were.
Please let Da-rae go.
I've lost everything.
What can I do?
I've lost everything!
How can we go back to the way it was?
No, Yi-gyeong.
There's a baby.
Think about the baby.
Please.
- Please stop this, okay?
- Yes.
Stop this.
Yi-gyeong!
Yi-gyeong.
What's going on?
What happened?
I'll tell you.
You all were
in this together, weren't you?
No, Yi-gyeong.
That's not it.
You were all in this together.
The building is on fire.
Let's not do this here.
Let's talk between us two.
I don't want to.
Let's talk everything out here.
This isn't what I wanted.
I never wanted
to put you in this position.
I just...
I wanted to escape from your mother.
Mom...
Did you kidnap me because of her?
Yes.
I just wanted to be with you.
I only thought of you.
I'm sorry.
Did you say
everything you need to?
Let Da-rae go first
and then let's talk.
I'll
explain everything one by one, okay?
Why not just die?
You should've just died.
Why have you lived this long?
I can't even choose to die.
Let's go home, Yi-gyeong.
We need to meet our baby.
This time,
I really want to protect our baby.
- Wow!
- Wait a minute, Hwal-sung!
- Be careful.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
What should we do now?
Then what about me?
Right.
Let's start over, okay?
Yi-gyeong!
Ah...
This is the police.
Freeze.
Put your hands up.
Hands up!
Officer...
Ugh!
I... I didn't do it.
Da-rae, are you okay?
Seon, are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Honey,
what do we do now?
I don't know either.
Da-rae.
I love you, Da-rae.
Seon, let's go down.
- Right.
- Da-rae, let's go down.
Okay.
Thanks to the man,
the woman survived.
Over here!
Are you okay?
Hey!
What's going on here?
Hey, who's the suspect?
Are the reporters here?
- Keep watching.
- Yes.
- You're here?
What's going on here?
This is crazy.
Seon, you still need
to get checked out at the hospital.
Are you okay?
Yes, but I think we need to
head to the hospital.
Understood.
About the building
catching fire,
a few days ago,
the repair guy came to check it out.
I sent him back
because it was too much money.
He definitely warned
that it was dangerous.
You really are Gi Su-jong.
I need to tell you something.
What is it?
Promise me you won't lie from now on.
Even if I were to be reborn,
I wouldn't lie to you. I'm serious.
When would you even be reborn?
When you die, that's it.
So you should have done better
while you are here.
You're right.
This way!
What's going on?
Once again, you feel in a deep sleep
after getting wasted.
Hwal-sung, what time is it now?
Right now?
Right now is now. What do you think?
Your wife's birthday.
Hurry over.
We still have a lot of drinks.
What's with him?
I had a nightmare. It was totally insane.
What was it about?
I mean, I don't even know where to start.
Anyway, it was a really terrifying dream.
Did the building prices drop or something?
No, that's not it.
You kidnapped Yi-gyeong.
To get money
from your mother-in-law.
But...
Did you really do nothing wrong?
Gi Su-jong,
snap out of it.
You've woken up.
Just rest today and you can go home.
- Yes.
Thank you.
Don't worry.
Your wife and daughter are safe.
I see.
What time is it now? How long has it been?
About ten hours have passed.
Not right now, but you'll need
to cooperate with the police inquiry.
It's a case with multiple casualties.
Casualties?
Min Hwal-sung has passed away.
Can I ask you something?
Why were you all at
Seyoon Building last night?
Just...
We just gathered there.
Jeon Yi-gyeong ordered Jang Dong-chul
to kidnap your daughter, it seems.
Is that true?
At Hye-yunsa,
there's CCTV footage of
the kidnapping scene.
I think
that's a misunderstanding.
What misunderstanding?
Well, you see,
Jeon Yi-gyeong
is like family to us.
There are no issues.
Jeon Yi-gyeong has woken up.
This is all
Gi Su-jong's doing.
Me getting kidnapped
and what happened with Oh Dong-ki
and my mom too,
it's all Gi Su-jong's fault!
Ms. Jeon Yi-gyeong,
we have evidence
that you kidnapped Da-rae.
That's true,
but I wasn't planning to do anything bad.
It's still kidnapping a minor!
I know.
I'll take my punishment.
But you need to catch Gi Su-jong.
I told you I found the culprit, right?
It's Gi Su-jong.
We need that evidence.
My phone.
My cell phone.
Where is my phone?
Or you can ask Da-rae about everything.
Da-rae knows all of this.
No, wait.
If you ask Hwal-sung,
he'll tell you everything.
What did your husband say...
Gi Su-jong said he killed my husband.
But suddenly,
he showed up at Seyoon Building.
He appeared and said he was wrong
and asked for forgiveness,
saying that he's sorry.
So if you ask Hwal-sung,
he'll tell you everything.
Wait a second.
So, Gi Su-jong killed your husband
and showed up at Seyoon Building?
Yes.
Well,
he died.
I confirmed it with my own eyes.
But, he came to save me.
Min Hwal-sung is the one
who fell from the roof, right?
Yes.
What? Is there something wrong?
Your husband has passed away.
What do you mean?
I just told you.
Hwal-sung came
to Seyoon Building.
So I thought he was dead,
but he came back alive.
To save me.
That's...
Let's just stop here for today.
So,
Jeon Yi-gyeong hired Jang Dong-chul
from Loan Heaven
to kidnap Da-rae, right?
Has the analysis finished
for the Hye-yun Company CCTV?
Yes, almost done...
Okay,
first check the relationship
between Jang Dong-chul and Jeon Yi-gyeong.
Also get the testimony
from Gi Su-jong's daughter.
What about Gi Su-jong?
Hey!
Why Gi Su-jong?
To dig up more baseless claims?
That's enough already. Come on.
- Hello?
- Honey.
Da-rae's been called in as a witness.
I guess Yi-gyeong said something.
Oh, then I need to explain things
to Da-rae so they can understand.
Is this right?
We should get the words straight
so that they don't suspect us,
and Yi-gyeong will be released too.
Da-rae's here.
Hang up.
Okay.
Da-rae.
The police called.
They want you to come in as a witness.
When are you going?
Not me.
I meant you, Da-rae.
Are you going to be okay?
You don't have to if it's too hard.
No, I'm fine.
It's something I have to do
for Aunt Yi-gyeong, too.
Okay.
First, let's eat.
Eat up.
My name is Kim Seon.
I admit to assisting my husband,
Gi Su-jong,
in the kidnapping of Jeon Yi-gyeong.
Jeon Yi-gyeong's abduction was the result
of the actions of Min Hwal-sung
and I, Gi Su-jong.
Would you like to move this video
to the trash?
MOVE TO TRASH
Have a good day.
My goodness.
I'm dying here.
Goodness.
But why is this site taking so long?
That's because
you're just too detailed.
Yes,
I can be a bit delicate.
- Oh, this thing...
- Oh, come on.
What are you doing leaving this here?
- It's raining. What if it gets wet?
- I left it there.
Why did you leave the hoe here too?
What is this?
Huh?
Call the police!
- It's someone's hand!
- Oh!
The phone!
- Hurry, get the phone!
- Oh, the phone!
Hurry up and call!
Where's the phone?
- What? What's going on?
- What is it?
It's a hand!
A human hand!
MAD CONCRETE DREAMS
Jang Hee-ju has been found dead.
You were with Jang Hee-ju all night
at the office.
I need to make 30 billion.
Without her,
Pyeong-buk Gwan will be taken care of.
I'm here to meet Yi-gyeong.
I think those guys might do something
to Yi-gyeong too.
Do you think for Gyun...
Did that person kill Gyun too?
You knew about this?
Got it.
What would you think
if a friend betrayed you?
Is it okay to just kill them?